So friends, today we will talk
about the stock of Ati Ducks. What support and resistance can be seen in the stock of Ati Ducks
for the next trading week,
today in this video we will talk about it.
If we talk about the stock here, then
we will see that this stock was seen
here in a clear down trend continuously,
earlier we were seeing a
pattern of lower low lower high in the stock here,
but then the stock
took support here, after which now
again we are seeing a continuous rise in the stock here, now
again we are seeing a pattern of higher high higher low in the stock here
and today also we have seen a rise in the stock at 0.60 here, so
from here let
us talk about the stock, from here if the
stock rises further, then
in the condition of this rise, we will
see the first resistance of 55 in the stock at this,
if the stock breaks this also, then
again a good rise and good buying can be
seen in this stock at this, after this now
we  563 in the stock here,
after this we will get 591 in the stock here
and if the stock breaks this too, then
6 in the stock here, after this we will get 50 in the
stock here and after this we can
also see levels up to 675 in the
stock from here, if the stock falls from here, then
in the condition of this fall, we will
get to see the guard of 513 in the stock here, support here, if the stock
breaks this, then from here we will get 501 in the stock
and then from here we can again
see levels up to 48 in the stock here,
like this next here is support, so there are
some important levels in the stock, you
can pay attention to these, there is no buy
sell holding advice in the rest of the video, the video is only
for educational purpose, thank you.